[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The lion is the largest member of the cat species.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which anatomical term defines the midline groove connecting the upper lip to the nose?", "correct_answer": "Philtrum", "incorrect_answers": ["Tachyon", "Edaphadium", "Serein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lanthanoids and actinoids are not included with the rest of the periodic table for convenience. Which series of elements are found in these two series, respectively?", "correct_answer": "La - Yb, Ac - No", "incorrect_answers": ["Ba - Lu, Ra - Lr", "La - Ac, Ac - Lu", "Fr - La, Cs - Ac"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the code name of Captain Hilts, the fictional character portrayed by Steve McQueen in The Great Escape?", "correct_answer": "The Cooler King", "incorrect_answers": ["The Forger", "The Mole", "The Scrounger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the rarest and most endangered of all wolves.", "correct_answer": "Red Wolf", "incorrect_answers": ["Ethiopian Wolf", "Black-backed Wolf", "Gray Wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Black wolf is actually a color variant of which wolf species?", "correct_answer": "Grey wolf", "incorrect_answers": ["White wolf", "None of these", "Brown wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The breathing sound of what animal was used for the breathing of the horrifying Tyrannosaurus rex in Steven Spielbergs 1993 science fiction thriller Jurassic Park?", "correct_answer": "Whale", "incorrect_answers": ["Alligator", "Rhinoceros", "Hippopotamus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Change the Roman numeral XL to a Hindu-Arabic numeral.", "correct_answer": "40", "incorrect_answers": ["70", "50", "60"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Friedkin directed a 2007 episode of this TV drama in which he again worked with To Live and Die in L.A.s star William Petersen.", "correct_answer": "CSI: Crime Scene Investigation", "incorrect_answers": ["Without a Trace", "Law and Order: Criminal Intent", "Law and Order"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1992 comedy film is the following quote from: A gun rack... a gun rack. I dont even own *a* gun, let alone many guns that would necessitate an entire rack. What am I gonna do... with a gun rack??", "correct_answer": "Waynes World", "incorrect_answers": ["Night at the Rocksbury", "Tommy Boy", "Superstar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the US First Ladies was named Sarah Childress. Who was she married to?", "correct_answer": "James K. Polk", "incorrect_answers": ["John Quincy Adams", "John Tyler", "Zachary Taylor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How fast can a black bear run?", "correct_answer": "48 km/hour", "incorrect_answers": ["61km/hour", "39 km/hour", "53 km/hour"]}]